Marcel Breuer
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Project Files, 1921-1986, Series 8:; (Boxes 8-23, 36-40, OVs 43-57; Reels 5720-5737; 27.6 linear feet)
  - Colleges and Universities, 1938-1981, 8.6:
    - St. John's Abbey and University, Collegeville, Minnesota, 1953-1981, 8.6.10:
      - Monastery Wing, 1953-1956 (Box 18, Reel 5727)
        - Photographs of plans, drawings, model, and construction (Box 18, Reel 5727, Frame 1271-1299)
          (2 photographs are of Breuer and Abbey officials at the construction site)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 18, Reel 5727, Frame 1300-1326)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior, (2 folders) (Box 18, Reel 5727, Frame 1327-1357)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior continued (Box 18, Reel 5728, Frame 11-27)
      - St. Thomas Aquinas Residence Hall (Student Residence Hall I), 1958-1959 (Box 18, Reel 5728)
        - Photographs of plans and drawings (Box 18, Reel 5728, Frame 29-35)
        - Photographs of construction, (2 folders) (Box 18, Reel 5728, Frame 36-59)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders) (Box 18, Reel 5728, Frame 60-87)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 18, Reel 5728, Frame 88-104)
      - Abbey Church and Bell Banner, 1953-1964 (Box 18, Reel 5728)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 18, Reel 5728, Frame 106-136)
        - Photographs of model, (2 folders) (Box 18, Reel 5728, Frame 137-168)
        - Photographs of construction, (11 folders) (Box 18, Reel 5728, Frame 169-332)
          (includes photo of Breuer on the construction site)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (5 folders) (Box 18, Reel 5728, Frame 333-)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (6 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame -454)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior, (10 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 455-594)
          (includes a photocopy from a damaged negative of a window by Josef Albers)
      - Library, 1960-1965 (Box 19, Reel 5728)
        - Photographs of plans, (2 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 596-612)
        - Photographs of drawings and model (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 613-626)
        - Photographs of construction, (5 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 627-666)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 667-685)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior, (3 folders; oversized material housed in Box 38) (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 686-719)
        - Oversized photographs of project, interior, (oversized material scanned with Box 19, Reel 5728, Frames 686-719) (Box 38, Reel 5728)
      - Science Hall and Auditorium, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Reel 5728)
        - Presentation book (Box BV 44, Reel 5728, Frame 721-742)
        - Photographs of plans and drawings (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 743-752)
        - Photographs of construction, (4 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 753-789)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 790-799)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 800-812)
      - Student Center and Swimming Pavilion. Photograph of a drawing, 1966 (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 813-815)
      - Ecumenical and Cultural Research Center, 1967 (Box 19, Reel 5728)
        - Photographs of plans and drawings (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 817-821)
        - Photographs of construction (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 822-831)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 832-837)
      - Student Residence Hall II, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Reel 5728)
        - Photograph of window design plans (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 839-841)
        - Photographs of construction, (5 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 842-871)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (4 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 872-910)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 911-919)
      - Gymnasium. Photographs of plans and drawings (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 920-923)
      - Sculpture The Athlete. Photographs of plans and drawings (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 924-943)
    - Sarah Lawrence College, Arts Center, Bronxville, New York, 1950-1977, 8.6.11:
      - Letters and contracts (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 945-958)
      - Photographs of plans, drawings, and model (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 959-969)
      - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 970-991)
      - Photographs of completed project, interior, (2 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5728, Frame 992-1008)
      - Negatives, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Color transparencies (Box 20, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1010-1064)
    - Smith College Competition, Dormitories, Northampton, Massachusetts, 1945, 8.6.12:
      - Photographs of plans, 1945, (oversized material housed in Box 38) (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1065-1069)
      - Negative, 1945 (Box 20, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Oversized photographs of plans, 1945, (oversized material scanned with Box 20, Reel 5728, Frames 1065-1069) (Box 38, Reel 5728)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo, Engineering and Applied Science Complex, Buffalo, New York, 1970, 8.6.13:
      - Photographs of plans, drawings, and model (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1070-1079)
      - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1080-1086)
      - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1087-1089)
      - Negatives and color transparencies (Box 20, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Vassar College, Dwight Ferry House Cooperative Dormitory, Poughkeepsie, New York, 1950-1952, 8.6.14:
      - Contract (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1091-1093)
      - Photographs of plans, drawings, and model (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1094-1110)
      - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (3 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1111-1144)
      - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1145-1154)
      - Negatives (Box 20, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Color transparencies (Box 20, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1155-1167)
    - University of Virginia, Physics Building, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1970-1972, 8.6.15:
      - Letters and contract, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1169-1222)
      - Photographs of plans (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1223-1226)
      - Negatives (Box 20, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Wheaton College Competition, Art Center, Norton, Massachusetts, 1938, 8.6.16:
      - Photographs of plans, drawings, and model, 1938, (oversized material housed in OV 48) (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1227-1245)
      - Negatives, 1938 (Box 20, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Yale University, Becton Center of Engineering and Applied Science, New Haven, Connecticut, 1964-1972, 8.6.17:
      - Letters and contract (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1247-1290)
      - Photographs of plans (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1291-1300)
      - Photographs of drawings, (oversized material housed in Box 38) (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1301-1304)
      - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1305-1330)
      - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1331-1340)
      - Negatives, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings (Box 20, Reel 5728, Frame 1341-1369)
      - Oversized photographs of drawings, (oversized material scanned with Box 20, Reel 5728, Frames 1301-1304) (Box 38, Reel 5728)
  - Museums and Galleries, 1963-1981, 8.7:
    This subseries consists of 5 project files concerning the construction of buildings for the exhibition and study of art and artifacts.
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, Education Wing, Cleveland, Ohio, 1967-1976, 8.7.1:
      - Letters and contracts, (3 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5729, Frame 13-96)
      - Photographs of plans, drawings, and construction, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5729, Frame 97-113)
      - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (5 folders; oversized material housed in Box 38) (Box 20, Reel 5729, Frame 114-165)
      - Photographs of completed project, interior, (4 folders; oversized material housed in Box 38) (Box 20, Reel 5729, Frame 166-222)
      - Negatives (Box 20, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Color transparencies (Box 20, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings, (5 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5729, Frame 223-301)
      - Press kit (Box 20, Reel 5729, Frame 302-339)
      - Printed report (Box 20, Reel 5729, Frame 341-344)
      - Oversized photographs of completed project, exterior, (oversized material scanned with Box 20, Reel 5729, Frames 114-165) (Box 38, Reel 5729)
      - Photographs of completed project, interior, (oversized material scanned with Box 20, Reel 5729, Frames 166-222) (Box 38, Reel 5729)
    - Heckscher Museum, Expansion Project, Huntington, New York, 1973-1980, 8.7.2:
      - Contract (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 347-382)
      - Photographs of plans (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 383-385)
    - Marlborough-Gerson Gallery, New York, New York, 1971, 8.7.3:
      - Letter Concerning Renovation, 1971 (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 386-387)
    - National Museum of American Amusement [location unknown], 1976, 8.7.4:
      - Blueprints, 1976 (Box OV 49, Reel 5729, Frame 388-391)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, New York, New York, 1963-1981, 8.7.5:
      - Letters and contracts (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 393-417)
      - Architect's report (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 418-435)
      - Presentation book of photographs of plans, (2 folders); (Oversized material housed in OV 49) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 436-474)
      - Photographs of drawings (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 475-483)
      - Photographs of construction site, (2 folders) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 484-503)
        (includes photos of visit by Breuer and Jacqueline Kennedy)
      - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (5 folders; oversized material housed in Box 38) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 504-544)
      - Photographs of completed project, interior, (5 folders; oversized material housed in Box 38) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 545-575)
        (includes 7 photographs of Breuer)
      - Negatives, (3 folders; oversized material housed in Box 38) (Box 21, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings, (12 folders) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 576-805)
      - Press kit (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 806-824)
      - Miscellaneous printed material (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 825-833)
      - Oversized presentation book of photographs of plans, (2 folders); (Oversized material scanned with Box 21, Reel 5729, Frames 436-474) (Box OV 49, Reel 5729)
      - Oversized photographs of completed project, exterior, (oversized material scanned with Box 21, Reel 5729, Frames 504-544) (Box 38, Reel 5729)
      - Oversized photographs of completed project, interior, (oversized material scanned with Box 21, Reel 5729, Frames 545-575) (Box 38, Reel 5729)
      - Oversized negatives, (see also Box 21) (Box 38, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
  - Convents, Churches, and Synagogues, 1957-1978, 8.8:
    This subseries consists of 6 project files concerning the construction of buildings for religious organizations.
    - Baldegg Convent, Mother House Institute near Lucerne, Switzerland, 1967-1975, 8.8.1:
      - Letters and contracts (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 836-865)
      - Photographs of plans, (oversized material housed in Box 39) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 866-880)
      - Photograph of a drawing, (oversized material housed in Box 39) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 881-884)
      - Photographs of construction (Box 21, Reel 5729)
        (includes photos of Breuer examining prefabricated concrete sections)
        - Contact sheet photographs of completed project, exterior and interior, (2 folders) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 886-920)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (7 folders; oversized material housed in Box 39) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 921-989)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior, (2 folders) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 990-1017)
        - Negatives (Box 21, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 21, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1018-1035)
      - Oversized photographs of plans, (oversized material scanned with Box 21, Reel 5729, Frames 866-880) (Box 39, Reel 5729)
      - Oversized photograph of a drawing, (oversized material scanned with Box 21, Reel 5729, Frames 881-884) (Box 39, Reel 5729)
      - Oversized photographs of completed project, exterior, (oversized material scanned with Box 21, Reel 5729, Frames 921-989) (Box 39, Reel 5729)
    - Olgiata Parish Church, Rome, Italy, 1968-1969, 8.8.2:
      - Letter and contract (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1037-1040)
      - Photographs of plans, drawing, and model (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1041-1056)
      - Photographs of proposed construction site, (4 folders) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1057-1093)
      - Negatives (Box 21, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Picture postcards of Chiesa di S. Giovanni Battista dell'Autostrada del Sole, Florence, Italy (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1094-1101)
    - St. Francis de Sales Church, Church and Rectory, Muskegon, Michigan, 1961-1978, 8.8.3:
      - Letters and contract (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1103-1118)
      - Presentation book (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1119-1148)
      - Photographs of plans (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1149-1162)
      - Photographs of drawings and model (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1163-1171)
      - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders; oversized material housed in Box 39) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1172-1208)
      - Photographs of completed project, interior, (oversized material housed in Box 39) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1209-1220)
      - Clippings, (3 folders) (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1221-1294)
      - Press Kit (Box 21, Reel 5729, Frame 1295-1323)
        (includes portrait photographs of Breuer, Herbert Beckhard, and Rev. Louis La Pres)
      - Press Kit, continued (Box 21, Reel 5730, Frame 10-18)
      - Oversized photographs of completed project, exterior, (oversized material scanned with Box 21, Reel 5729, Frames 1172-1208) (Box 39, Reel 5729)
      - Oversized photographs of completed project, interior, (oversized material scanned with Box 21, Reel 5729, Frames 1209-1220) (Box 39, Reel 5729)
    - St. Luke's Church, Fairport, New York, 1964-1965, 8.8.4:
      - Contract, photographs of plans, and clippings (Box 21, Reel 5730, Frame 20-33)
    - Temple B'Nai Jeshurun, Short Hills, Millburn Township, New Jersey, 1961- 1965, 8.8.5:
      - Letters and contract (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 36-55)
      - Photographs of plans (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 56-60)
      - Photographs of drawings and model (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 61-75)
      - Negatives, (2 folders) (Box 22, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 76-123)
    - Westchester Reform Temple, Scarsdale, New York, 1957, 8.8.6:
      - Photographs of plans and drawings (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 125-126)
      - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 127-139)
      - Photographs of completed project, interior, (2 folders) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 140-155)
  - Memorials, 1945-1975, 8.9:
    This subseries consists of 3 project files concerning the construction of commemorative structures.
    - Unidentified memorial, photograph of a model, 1945 (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 158)
    - Cambridge War Memorial, Cambridge, Massachusetts, photographs of plans, drawing, and model, 1945 (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 160-165)
    - Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial, Washington, D.C., 1964-1975 (Box 22, Reel 5730)
      - Contract (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 167-185)
      - Photographs of plans and drawings, (oversized material housed in Box 39) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 186-196)
      - Photographs of model (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 197-208)
      - Negatives, (2 folders) (Box 22, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings, (2 folders) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 209-262)
      - Press kit (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 263-288)
      - Oversized photographs of plans and drawings, (oversized material scanned with Box 22, Reel 5730, Frames 186-196) (Box 39, Reel 5730)
  - Office Buildings, 1961-1978, 8.10:
    This subseries consists of 10 project files concerning the construction of buildings for corporate enterprises.
    - American Press Institute, Conference Center, Reston, Virginia, 1972-1978, 8.10.1:
      - Photographs of plans and drawing (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 291-296)
      - Contact sheet photographs of completed project, exterior and interior (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 297-298)
      - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders; oversized materials housed in Box 39) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 299-310)
      - Photographs of completed project, interior, (2 folders) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 311-324)
      - Negatives (Box 22, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings and brochure (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 325-343)
      - Oversized photographs of completed project, exterior, (oversized materials scanned with Box 22, Reel 5730, Frames 299-310) (Box 39, Reel 5730)
    - Boston Office Building, 60 State Street, Boston, Massachusetts, 1969-1972, 8.10.2:
      - Letters and contracts, (4 folders) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 345-487)
      - Photographs of plans, (2 folders) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 488-501)
      - Photographs of drawings (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 502-510)
      - Photographs of model and aerial view of site (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 511-522)
      - Negatives, (2 folders; oversized material housed in Box 39) (Box 22, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Booklet (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 523-533)
      - Oversized negatives, (see also Box 22) (Box 39)
    - Cleveland Trust Company, Bank and Office Building, Cleveland, Ohio, 1967-1973, 8.10.3:
      - Letters and contracts, (3 folders) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 535-672)
      - Photographs of plans, (3 folders) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 673-689)
      - Photographs of drawings (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 690-692)
      - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (4 folders; oversized materials housed in Box 39) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 693-729)
      - Photographs of completed project, interior, (2 folders; oversized materials housed in Box 39) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 730-745)
      - Negatives and color transparency (Box 22, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 746-767)
      - Brochures (Box 39, Reel 5730, Frame 768-798)
      - Oversized photographs of completed project, exterior, (oversized materials scanned with Box 22, Reel 5730, Frames 693-729) (Box 39, Reel 5730)
      - Oversized photographs of completed project, interior, (oversized materials scanned with Box 22, Reel 5730, Frames 730-745) (Box 39, Reel 5730)
    - Common Market Center, Brussels, Belgium, undated, 8.10.4:
      - Printed schematic drawings of plan de situation, plans d'implantation, plan général, élévations, vue d'ensemble, and salles de réunions (Box OV 49, Reel 5730, Frame 799-806)
    - European Investment Bank Kirchberg Plateau, Luxembourg, 1971-1975, 8.10.5:
      - Letters, 1971-1973, (3 folders) (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 808-934)
      - Letters, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 935-985)
      - Contract (Box 22, Reel 5730, Frame 986-1043)
      - Miscellaneous reports, (2 folders) (Box 23, Reel 5730, Frame 1045-1157)
      - Bouwcentrum (engineers') reports (Box 23, Reel 5730, Frame 1158-1362)
      - Bouwcentrum (engineers') reports, continued (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 11-408)
      - Denys Lasdun & Partners (architects') reports, (5 folders) (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 409-683)
      - Cost estimate reports (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 684-735)
      - Minutes of meetings (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 736-853)
      - Photographs of plans (Box 39, Reel 5731, Frame 854-876)
      - Photographs of model (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 877-883)
      - Photographs of construction site (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 884-893)
      - Negatives (Box 23, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Brochures (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 894-928)
    - Grand Central Air Rights Building, 175 Park Avenue, New York, New York, 1963-1978, 8.10.6:
      - Letters and contract, (10 folders) (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 930-1252)
      - Portrait photographs of Breuer and Herbert Beckhard [?] (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 1253-1255)
      - Photographs of plans (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 1256-1275)
      - Photographs of drawings, (oversized material housed in Box 39) (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 1276-1289)
      - Photographs of model (Box 39, Reel 5731, Frame 1290-1300)
      - Photographs of construction site, (2 folders; includes copy prints, 1905) (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 1301-1348)
      - Negatives (Box 23, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Album of clippings (Box 23, Reel 5731, Frame 1349-1396)
      - Album of clippings, continued (Box 23, Reel 5732, Frame 11-24)
      - Clippings, (3 folders) (Box 23, Reel 5732, Frame 25-94)
      - Press releases (Box 23, Reel 5732, Frame 95-99)
      - Oversized photographs of drawings, (oversized material scanned with Box 39, Reel 5731, Frames 1276-1289) (Box 39, Reel 5731)
    - Harrison-State Development Corporation, Office Building, Bristol Center, Syracuse, New York, 1968-1971, 8.10.7:
      - Letters and contract, (3 folders) (Box 23, Reel 5732, Frame 101-270)
      - Photographs of plans and drawings (Box 23, Reel 5732, Frame 271-276)
      - Negatives (Box 23, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings (Box 23, Reel 5732, Frame 277-287)
    - Office Building for Airport Street, Riyadh, Kingdom of Saudi Arabia, undated, 8.10.8:
      - Photographs of drawings, (oversized material housed in Box 39) (Box 23, Reel 5732, Frame 288-296)
      - Oversized photographs of drawings, (oversized material scanned with Box 23, Reeel 5732, Frames 288-296) (Box 39, Reel 5732)
    - One Charles Center, Baltimore, Maryland, 1961, 8.10.9:
      - Photographs of plans and drawing (Box 23, Reel 5732, Frame 298-302)
      - Photographs of model (Box 23, Reel 5732, Frame 303-317)
      - Negatives and color transparencies (Box 23, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings (Box 23, Reel 5732, Frame 318-319)
    - Xerox Corporation [location unknown], undated [1982?], 8.10.10:
      - Photograph of a drawing (Box 39, Reel 5732, Frame 321-322)
  - Industrial and Factory Properties, 1929-1984, 8.11:
    This subseries consists of 27 project files concerning the construction of facilities for manufacturing products.
    Files are arranged alphabetically
    - Armstrong Rubber Company, New Haven, Connecticut, 1968-1969, 8.11.1:
      - Letters (Box 24, Reel 5732, Frame 328-339)
      - Photographs of plans (Box 24, Reel 5732, Frame 340-353)
      - Photographs of drawings (Box 24, Reel 5732, Frame 354-356)
      - Photographs of construction (Box 24, Reel 5732, Frame 357-362)
      - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (5 folders; oversized material housed in Box 39) (Box 24, Reel 5732, Frame 363-404)
      - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 24, Reel 5732, Frame 405-413)
      - Negatives, (oversized material housed in Box 39) (Box 24, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Clippings (Box 24, Reel 5732, Frame 414-417)
      - Oversized photographs of completed project, exterior, (oversized material scanned with Box 24, Reel 5732, Frame 363-404) (Box 39, Reel 5732)
      - Oversized negatives, (see also Box 39) (Box 39, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - BAFO Warehouse, Springfield, Virginia, 1977, 8.11.2:
      - Letters (Box 24, Reel 5732, Frame 418-424)